sabserial.com 2018-03-11

# 

**Sabserial.com** respects the privacy of users and is committed to protect their privacy in all respects. PEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY BEFORE USING THIS WEBSITE. This Agreement is made between Sabserial.com and you as a site visitor.

The present privacy policy governs the online information collection practices of Sabserial.com. Specifically, it outlines the types of information that we gather about you from your use of the Sabserial.com website (the "Site"), and the ways in which we use and don't use this information. This privacy policy, including our children's privacy statement, does not apply to any information you may provide to us or that we may collect offline and/or through other means. To submit your comments on the Site where personal information is requested, you may be asked for your name and email address. You hereby agree that all information you provide to Sabserial regarding your identification shall be truthful, accurate, and complete.

This privacy policy details important information regarding the use and disclosure of user and/ or member information collected on the Site. Sabserial provides this privacy policy to help you make an informed decision about whether to use or discontinue using the Site.This privacy policy is incorporated into and is subject to the Sabserial's Terms of Use. Your use of the Sabserial Site and any personal information you provide on the Site remains subject to the terms of this privacy policy and our Terms of Use.Please note that any video, image, comment or other content posted on the Site becomes published content and is not considered personally identifiable information which is subject to this privacy notice.

**THIRD-PARTY ADVERTISEMENT**

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/). 

**OUR COMMITMENT TO DATA SECURITY**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**OUR COMMITMENT TO CHILDRENS' PRIVACY**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under age of 13, unless provided necessary Gaurdian Permission in written form. (COPA)

**CONTACT INFORMATION**

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, send us an email at [privacy@sabserial.com](mailto:privacy@sabserial.com)
